米奇？
Mitch?
阿什利？
Ashley?
你们在吗？
You out here?
拜托 伙计们
Come on, guys.
你们在哪儿？
Where are you?
有人吗？
Hello?
布洛迪 阿什利和托德 他们死了
- Brodie. - Ashley and Todd, they're dead.
温蒂 他们死了
Wendy, they're dead.
布洛迪 我们得团结起来 我们没有机会 知道吗？
Pull it together. - Pull it together? We don't have a chance.
我们得离开这里 马上 不行 布洛迪 我们不能走
- We have to get out of here. - No, we are not leaving.
我们得找到我姐姐 不
- We have got to find my sister. - No.
不 我现在就要离开这里 布洛迪
- No, I am getting out of here right now. - Brodie!
布洛迪 给我回来 布洛迪
Brodie get back here! Brodie!
老天 你个混球
God, you son of a bitch.
停机 见鬼的这是什么？
Cut. What the hell was that?
谢了
Thanks.
给你的 谢了 沃尔特
Here you go. - Thanks, Walter.
别… 别记录那个
Don't mark that.
都很不错 泰拉 非常棒
It's all good, Tara. That was great.
嗯 我们再来一遍
Uh, let's do it again.
嗯 也许我们该提高那声尖叫？
Uh, maybe we try dialing up that scream, huh?
我知道 我知道 我只是… 只是那个网球让我无法集中
I know, I know. I'm just-I'm having trouble with the tennis ball.
你知道 那只是为摄像机聚准用的
Oh, you know what? That is for CG registration.
当伊万和做特效的同僚弄好之后 将会看起来非常恐怖
Now, when Ivan and the FX guys are done, it is going to look terrifying.
你还要再看一下剧情概括吗？不用了 没关系 我会找到感觉的
- Wanna look at the concept sketches again? - No, that's okay. I'll find it, I'll find it.
我知道你会的 亲爱的 恩？好
I know you will, huh? Okay.
再来一次 伙计们 10分钟调试镜头和音效
Going again, everybody. Ten-minute reload for camera and sound.
不 朋友 我告诉你 一个人在布景后面或者收工后干活…
Wow, man. I'm telling you, working alone behind the sets or after wrap...
有时我会有种古怪的感觉
- Yeah. - ...I catch this weird vibe sometimes.
像哪种的？
Oh, like what?
呒… 像被什么东西注视着
Like something's watching.
算了吧 嘿
- Come on. - Hey...
就像拍摄这样的电影？古怪的谣言一定会有的
working on a movie like this, weird crap's bound to happen.
弗兰克认为场景有鬼魂出没 就像 真的一样
Frankie thinks the stage is haunted. Like, for real.
我说的一切 他们称为胡扯 一旦完工 我就离开这里
All I'm saying is, they call wrap, I get done and I get out of here.
迅速的
Fast.
那家伙肯定是疯了
That guy is definitely off his meds.
布洛迪 回来
Brodie, come back.
你个混球
You son of a bitch.
布洛迪 回来 你个混球
Brodie, come back, you son of a bitch.
有人吗？
Hello?
伙计们？
Guys?
好了 这不好玩
Come on, it's not funny.
好吧
Okay.
哈哈 很有趣
Ha-ha. Very funny.
有人吗？
Hello?
谁在那里？
Who's there?
这就是我想听到的
Now, that's what I'm talking about.
[邪恶力量 第2季第18集]
1927年开园以来
First opened in 1927...
在80年间一直都在
the lot has been in continuous operation...
持续运作
for eight decades.
嗨 你知道这里就是拍的地方吗？(1982年美国电影)
Hey, you know this is where they filmed Creepshow?
现在右手边这里就是星谷
Now, to the right here is Stars Hollow.
是电视剧的摄影棚
It's the setting for the television series Gilmore Girls.
如果我们幸运的话
And if we're lucky, we might even catch...
甚至能一睹几个电视剧的明星
one of the show's stars.
来吧
Come on.
先逛完再说啊
Let's finish the tour.
然后这里是纽约大道
And then up to the right here we have...
就是在这儿取景的 (1993年美国电影)
New York Avenue, and that's where they shot Lois and Clark.
萨姆 快看 是马特达蒙
Sam, check it out, it's Matt Damon.
好吧 我很确信他不是马特达蒙 是 是他
- Yeah, pretty sure that's not Matt Damon. - No, it is.
那好 马特达蒙刚刚 捡起扫帚开始扫街
Well, Matt Damon just picked up a broom and started sweeping.
是的 他可能正在研究 一个角色或什么的
Well, he's probably researching a role or something.
我可不这么看
Uh, I don't think so.
嗨 这边 我想第9摄影棚在那里
Hey, this way. Uh, I think Stage 9's over here.
来吧 伙计 继续走这路 不 过来 我们得干活了
- Come on, man. Let's keep going this way. - No, come on, we gotta work.
天那 伙计 是你要来的洛杉矶 是啊 来休假的
You wanted to come to L.A. Yeah, for vacation.
我的意思是游泳池和电影明星 不是工作
I mean, swimming pools and movie stars. Not to work.
是不是游泳池才适合你 迪恩？
Does this seem like swimming-pool weather to you, Dean?
实际上是加拿大人 是的
- I mean, it's practically Canadian. - Yeah.
我刚刚意识到 你知道的
I just figured that after everything that happened with...
麦迪逊事件之后 你也许应该休息恢复一下 仅此而已
Madison, you could use a little R and R.
也许我只想工作 迪恩 也许这可以让我的注意力 不集中在那件事上
Well, maybe I wanna work. It keeps my mind off things.
好吧 好吧 好的
Okay. Okay. All right.
那么这个工作人员 他… 他是死在摄影棚里的？
So this crew guy, what did he-? He died on set?
是的 谣言如燎原般传的飞快
Yeah, rumor's spreading like wildfire online.
他们说摄影棚常有鬼魂出没
They're saying the set's haunted.
促狭鬼？
What, like Poltergeist?
可能是促狭鬼 不 不 不 是电影
- Could be a poltergeist. - No, no, no. The movie Poltergeist.
你对文化遗产一无所知 是吗？
You know nothing of your cultural heritage, do you?
谣传拍摄的摄影棚被诅咒了的
It was rumored that the set of Poltergeist was cursed.
他们用人骨做道具
That they used real human bones as, uh, props.
好像至少有3个演员死在那里了
Like, at least three of the actors died in it.
是的 也许有那样的事情
Yeah, it might be something like that.
好吧 那个工作人员 他叫什么名字？弗兰克迦夫
- So this crew guy, what's his name? - Frank Jaffy.
你拿到死亡证明或者 是验尸官报告了吗？
Frank Jaffy, you got a death certificate or a coroner's report?
不 但这是洛杉矶 明白吗？那可能不是他的真名
Well, no, but, uh, it's L.A., you know? Might not even be his real name.
但发现尸体的那个女孩说她 看到了些东西
But the girl who found him, she said she saw something.
若应若现的影子
A vanishing figure.
那女孩叫什么？泰拉本斯莉
- What's the girl's name? - Uh, Tara Benchley.
泰拉本斯莉？
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Tara Benchley?
那个饰演和 的泰拉本斯莉？
From FeardotCom and Ghost Ship, Tara Benchley?
伙计 干嘛不早说？
Dude, why didn't you say so?
你现在突然进入角色了？
Well, so now you're suddenly onboard?
我想说 我是她的影迷
I'm just-I mean, I'm a fan of her work.
这真不错
It's very good.
不 你看 别弄错了 在工作室的每个人都 热爱自己的工作
Look, don't get me wrong. Everyone at the studio loves the dailies.
包括我自己 我只是期望如果能…
Myself included. We were just wondering if it could be...
你懂的 再亮一点
you know, a little brighter.
再亮一点？是的 杰伊 多一点色彩
- Brighter? - Yeah, Jay. More color.
麦克基 你知道我在说什么 你是这种问题的专家
McG, you know what I'm saying. You're the master.
布莱德 这是部恐怖片 谁说恐怖就一定要阴暗？
- Brad, this is a horror movie. - And who says horror has to be dark?
这有种压抑的感觉 你不这么觉得吗？
It's just-It's sort of depressing. Don't you think?
嗯 不好意思 那个穿绿衬衫的朋友
Uh, excuse me, uh, green-shirt guy.
对 对 是你 过来
Yeah, yeah, you, come here.
你能从小店给我买
Could you get me a...
一杯奶昔吗？
uh, smoothie from craft?
你要从谁那里买什么？
You want a what from who?
你是个私人助理 这是你要做的事
You are a PA. This is what you do.
好的 好的 他… 呃…
Yeah, yeah, he, uh...
一杯奶昔马上就来
One smoothie coming right up.
什么是私人助理？我想某种意义上就是奴隶
- What's a PA? - I think they're kind of like slaves.
他们什么样人的 都会请进来干活 恩？
They'll let anybody into this business, huh?
对 把其中一个手柄放那里 可以
Yeah, one of the grips left that. That's good right there.
朋友们 过来 对 开始 了
Hey, guys. Come here. All right, let's go, people.
谢谢你
Thanks, man.
所以当塔拉说她的台词时 我就向前走
So when Tara's saying her lines, can I step forward...
然后让这个新的地方成为我的新标记？对对对 随你便
and make this new spot my new mark? Sure, sure, sure, treat yourself.
继续 请安静
Go ahead. Quiet, please.
安静 准备计时
Quiet, hold the bell.
灯光
Lights.
控制噪音 我们在拍摄
Hold the noise, we're rolling.
6章6场6幕 开始
Six, take six. Mark.
准备
Frame.
好吧 我们为什么不从 "来吧 这会很有趣的"这里开始？开机
Why don't we take it from "Come on, it'll be fun." And action.
来吧 这会很有趣的
Come on, it'll be fun.
也许你明天能搞定
Maybe you can finish this tomorrow?
老天 现在我真的很恨你 停机
- I hate you so much right now. - Cut.
非常好
Very nice.
所以呢？哪里都找不到电动势信号
So? - No EMF anywhere.
太棒了 那么 你怎么看？
Great. So, what do you think?
我认为作为一个 私人助理很差劲
Well, I think being a PA sucks.
看这些人吃的东西？简直是在跟我开玩笑… 你看看这些吃的
But the food these people get, are you kidding me? Look at these things.
它们就像是 迷你菲利牛排干酪三明治 它们很美味
They're like miniature Philly cheesesteak sandwiches. Their delicious.
也许晚些时候吧
Maybe later.
那个死亡的工作人员你查出什么了？
What did you find out about the dead crew guy?
呃… 弗兰克·迦夫那天第一次上班
Uh, Frank Jaffy was just filling in for the day.
这里没有人认识他和知道他住在哪里
Nobody here knew him or where he lived.
不错 你找到的和我一样多
Oh, great. So you found out as much as I did.
- 不是我… - 嗨 伙计们
- Not quite I-Hey, guys.
哦 嗨
Oh.Hey.
它们很棒
They're wonderful.
听着 我的确找到了一些关于 9号摄影棚的历史资料
Listen, I did dig up some stuff about Stage 9's history.
- 是吗？- 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
过去的80年里有4人死在这里
Four people died messy here over 80 years.
两起自杀和两起致命事故
Two suicides and two fatal accidents.
- 当中的每一个都可能是复仇的鬼魂 - 是的
- Any of those could be a vengeful spirit. - Yeah.
只是得把范围缩小一点
Just gotta narrow it down more.
我马上就去处理这个问题
I'll get right on that.
你是不是也应该拿一份这个？
Are you supposed to get one of these?
我… 我真的不知道自己应该做什么
I don't really know what I'm doing so-
第一天？
First day?
是的 我的新开始
Yeah, my big break.
你知道吗 我知道这样说真的不合适 但我是一个狂热的影迷
You know, I know it's really uncool to say this, but I'm a big fan.
我非常喜欢你在"超灵恶巫"中的表演
I loved you in Boogeyman.
哦 上帝啊 糟透了的剧本
Oh, God. What a terrible script.
但是 谢谢你 是的
Uh, but thank you. Yeah.
你发现了他 对吗 那个死了的人？
You found him, right, the dead guy?
很抱歉 你可能并不想谈及这个
I'm sorry, you probably don't wanna talk about this.
不 没有 事实上
No, actually it's...
这… 这没关系的 这里没什么人会过多的谈起那件事
It's okay, but nobody around here really brings it up very much.
我想他们都吓坏了 我都快有些精神崩溃了
I think they're all scared I'm gonna have some kind of breakdown.
那一定是非常可怕
That must have been awful.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
那非常恐怖
It was horrible.
很多的血… 从他的眼睛流出来…
There-There was all this blood coming from his eyes...
从他的嘴里流出来… 还有 呃…
and from his mouth, and, uh...
我还看到了这个 呃…
I saw this, um...
什么？
What?
我看到幽灵幻象
I saw this shape.
告诉你实话… 我不知道我到底
To tell you the truth, I don't know actually...
看到了什么 我只是知道我看到了
what I saw. I just know I saw it.
- 给你 塔拉 - 谢谢 沃尔特
- Here you go, Tara. - Thanks, Walter.
那么这个… 这个叫弗兰克的工作人员 你跟他熟吗？
Uh, so this crew guy, Frank. I mean, did you know him?
不 不太熟悉
Uh, no. Not that well.
这很古怪 好像这里没有谁 真正熟悉那个家伙
That's funny. It's like no one around here actually knew the guy.
- 我有他的照片 - 你有吗？
- I've got his picture. Um... - You do?
是的 我给每个工作人员都照了快照
Yeah, I take Polaroid's of all the crew.
只是那些在拍戏的时候… 你用来消磨时间所做的事
It's just one of those things you do to kill time on set.
就在那里
Um, right there.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
- 杰勒德圣詹姆士？- 有什么事？
- Gerard St. James? - Yes.
你还活着
You're still alive.
- 你不是弗兰克·迦夫 - 呃… 不是
- And you're not Frank Jaffy. Uh, no.
你曾经… 曾经在 中饰演过4号沙漠士兵
You were Desert Soldier #4 in Metalstorm: Destruction of Jared-Syn?
- 是的 - 我知道我认出了你
- I was. I knew I recognized you.
我是个狂热的影迷
I am a huge fan. Ha-ha.
我是说 你转身就变成了飞船事故的受害者
Your turn as a tractor-crash victim in Critters 3?
- 怪物3 - 哇哦
- Critters 3. - Wow.
- 是啊 - 好的 请 请进
- Yeah. - All right, well, please. Come in.
谢谢
Thanks.
是的 是制片人… 我是说 他们把我带过去 去装扮成弗兰克的
Yeah, it was the producers. I mean, they brought me in for the day to play Frank.
- 只是想伪造你的死亡？- 影片的造势而已…
- Just to fake your death? - Well, rumors of a haunted film set.
免费的宣传 尤其是当你在拍摄 一部恐怖片的时候
Free publicity. Especially when you're making a horror movie.
我是说这会儿 事情已经在互联网上传遍了
I mean, uh, it's already all over the Internet.
是的 我们知道
Yeah, we know.
这个时代 充斥了新媒体的概念 宣传造势
Well, these days, it's all about new media. Building buzz.
他们说
They say...
我是新的
I'm the new Lonelygirl.
- 谁？- 那么泰拉看到的鬼影呢？
- Who? - And the ghost Tara saw?
通过发射器放射到屏幕上的
Projected on a screen of diffusion.
这样的扰乱演员的精神… 是不是有些残酷了呢？
Isn't that kind of cruel? Messing with their heads like that?
我只是扮演角色 我不写剧本
Hey, I just play the part. I don't write the script.
说到这个… 下个月在哥斯达米加…
Speaking of, I'm playing Willy...
的独立影院中上映的一部 名为的电影中… 我饰演威利
in a dinner-theater production of Salesman at Costa Mesa all next month.
带着这个礼卷会得到 一份免费的胡椒牛排
You get a free pepper steak with the coupon.
等一下…
Ha.
如果你在公共场所露面 难道不会让造势不攻自破吗？
Well, if you're seen in public, won't that ruin the hoax?
哦 拜托
Please. Ha.
弗兰克和威利 完全不同的角色
Frank and Willy, totally different characters.
知道吗？
You know what?
非常感谢你 圣杰姆斯先生 虽然他一直唠叨不休
Thanks very much, Mr. St. James. It was just nagging at us, you know.
但是我们… 我们非常高兴… 你知道的
But we're very glad that, you know...
你还活着并且很好
you're alive and well.
好的
Yeah.
毫无疑问
Absolutely.
我想问问你… 和理查德·摩尔一起工作感觉如何？
Hey, uh, I wanted to ask you, what was it like working with Richard Moll?
金属风暴 他饰演希拉克 独眼巨人族的国王
Metalstorm. He was Hurok, king of the Cyclops people.
绅士中的绅士
Gentleman's gentleman.
是吗？
Yeah?
好的 胡椒牛排
All right. Pepper steak.
我们一定是在读那本书的时候… 把他们引回来了
When we read from that book, we must've brought them back.
从地狱中引回来了
Back from hell.
这无所谓
It doesn't matter.
在我们找到温蒂和她的妹妹之前 我们哪儿也不去 明白了吗？
We're not going anywhere until we find Wendy and her sister. Got it?
很好 现在 让我们大家都忙起来
Good. Now, let's get busy.
停机
Cut.
非常好
Very nice work. Mark it.
声音不对 我听到了某种回声
No good for sound. I'm getting some kind of feedback.
回到第一个
Back to one.
又一个昂贵的声音延迟
Another costly sound delay.
- 好了 大伙 我们要再录制一遍声音 - 谢谢大家
- We're going again for sound, people. - Thank you.
不 不 不 你瞧 这是很棒的一场 真的 不同凡响
No, no, no, look, see, it's great scene. Really. Dynamite...
但是我还是有一些… 不… 不是问题 只是些疑问
but I still got a few-Not-Not problems, just questions.
像哪种的？
Like what?
其中一件事是…
Well, for one thing...
剧情的规则不太适合我
the rules aren't really landing for me.
比如 当孩子们咏唱拉丁圣歌的时候… 那样就会让鬼魂出现吗？
Like, the kids do this Latin chant and that makes the ghost show up?
是的
Yeah.
如果鬼魂在地狱中 他们是如何听到圣歌的呢？
See, but if the ghosts are in hell, how do they hear the chanting?
我意思是 如何听到的 他们有顺风耳吗？
I mean, what, do they have super hearing?
这是个逻辑上的矛盾 剧情的规则没有逻辑可循
Well, it's a logic bump. The rules don't track.
马蒂 你是作者
Marty, you're the writer.
放进去个解说员如何？
What if I throw in an explainer?
好 那太棒了 我得去检查一条留言
Yeah, that'd be super. Excuse me, I gotta check some messages.
自大狂
Suits.
麦克基看到这个了吗？
Has McG seen this?
我喜欢这整体的身体彩绘 黑和白的配衬 但是 哦 我…
I like the whole body-paint, black-and-white thing, but, gee...
我不认为脖子上的那些伤口… 可以在摄像机上看清楚
I don't think those neck wounds are really gonna read on camera.
伤口得是红色的
They need to be red.
你知道我在说什么吗？
You know what I'm saying?
嗨 杰伊 我要和化妆师谈一谈
Hey, Jay? I need you to speak to Makeup right away.
什么事？
Yeah?
等一下
Wait up.
我们一定是在读了那本书的时候… 把他们引回来了
When we read from that book, we must've brought them back.
从地狱中引回来了
Back from hell.
但是我不明白 如果鬼魂在地狱中 他们是如何听到圣歌的呢？
But I don't understand. If they were in hell, how could they hear?
他们一定有顺风耳
They must have super hearing.
这是哇
What the...? Whoa!
噢 天呐
Oh, jeez.
- 温蒂？- 哦 米奇 上帝啊 你还活着
Wendy. - Oh, Mitch. God, you're alive.
你不会这么容易就把我甩掉的
You couldn't get rid of me that easy.
争论 争论 争论
Rumble, rumble, rumble!
盐 知道吗 我们需要盐
Salt. Okay, we need salt.
我在书中读到过 盐可以让鬼魂远离
I read in that book that it keeps ghosts away.
桑德拉 洛根 你们检查后面
Sandra, Logan, you guys check the back.
那个可怜的混蛋自杀了 说真的…
Jay, the poor bastard killed himself...
我们难道不应该 关闭摄影棚或者什么吗？
like, for real. Shouldn't we shut it down or something?
我们已经在吃早餐的时候 为他默哀了一会儿了
We had a moment of silence for him at breakfast.
他只是一个工作室的家伙而已
He was just a studio guy. Come on.
嘘
Shh.
- 我爱你 - 我知道
- I love you. - I know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们… 我们能不能停机或者什么？
Can we-? Can we cut or something?
呃… 是 停机 停机
Uh, uh, yeah, cut. Cut!
停机
That's a cut.
只有我能说停机
Only I can say, "cut."
嗨 怎么了？
Hey, what's up?
我只是有一点心烦意乱
I'm sorry, I'm just a little upset.
这里发生了这么多事 谁能责备你呢？
With everything that's been going on around here, who can blame you, huh?
我只是不能把我的精神 集中在剧本对话上
I just can't wrap my head around the dialogue.
你知道吗？盐 难道听起来不傻吗？
You know, salt? Doesn't that sound silly?
我意思是说 为什么一个鬼会惧怕盐呢？
I mean, why would a ghost be afraid of salt?
好的 呃…
Okay, um...
- 马蒂 - 哟
- Marty. - Yo.
你怎么想的？
What do you think?
不是非盐不娶 你想要什么？我们还要继续谈论调味品吗？
I'm not married to salt. What do you want? We still sticking with condiments?
只是听起来有些不同 并没有变好
Mm, just sounds different. Not better.
- 一个鬼还会惧怕什么其他东西呢？- 哦 你一定是在和我开玩笑
- What else would a ghost be scared of? - Uh, you gotta be kidding me.
鬼会怕什么？
What would a ghost be scared of?
也许是霰弹枪
Maybe, uh-Maybe shotguns.
那比盐还要不合乎逻辑
Okay, that makes even less sense than salt.
这些人都是白痴
These people are idiots.
- 沃尔特做为一个私人助理 脾气有点暴躁 恩？- 这里怎么样了？
- Walter's a little testy for a PA, huh? - How's it going in here?
很好 达拉的演技又有提高了
It's going good. Tara's stepped up her performance.
我认为是利用情景记忆得以提升的
Probably from all the sense memory she's drawing on.
- 情景记忆？- 是的
- Sense memory? - Yeah.
迪恩 当我问你这里进行得如何的时候
Dean.When I ask how it's going here,
我所说的是案子 好吗？
I'm talking about the case, right?
我们并不是真的在这里工作
We don't really work here.
知道吗 我以为你讨厌做私人助理的工作
You know, I thought you hated being a PA.
我不知道 也并不是太坏 我感觉我是剧组中的一员了
I don't know. It's not so bad. I kind of feel like part of the team.
这个不错 墨西哥卷？味道棒级了
It's good. Oh, taquito? They're wonderful.
不了 呃… 听着 我偷溜进了停尸房
No, um, listen, I conned my way into the morgue.
- 怎么样 - 新闻报道是对的
- And? - News reports are right.
布拉德死了 毫无疑问
Brad's a doornail, no question.
收到 对不起 什么？
Copy that. Sorry, what?
- 收到？- 你刚刚说什么？
- Copy that? - What'd you say?
- 新闻报道是属实的 布拉德死了 - 他们都知道了
- News reports are right. Brad's a doornail. - They're aware.
- 谁都知道了？- 对不起 你刚刚说什么？
- Who's aware? - Sorry, what were you saying?
呃 呃 新闻报道是属实的 布拉德死了 这件事毫无疑问
Uh, what-The newspaper's right. Brad's a doornail, no question about it.
我猜我们没有掉下去是好事
It's a good thing we didn't skip town.
到这里来 我想让你听点东西
Oh, come here. I want you to hear something.
收到 马上就到
Copy that. On my way.
嗨 戴夫 你能把你之前 放给我听的东西再放一次吗？
Hey, Dave, can you play him that thing you were playing me earlier?
当然
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
这没关系 在我们找到温蒂和她的姐姐之前 我们不会离开
Doesn't matter, we're not leaving till we...
超自然电子异象 从布拉德布景台跳水的那晚发出的
E.V.P. From the night of Brad's stage dive.
突然出现 我在布景台上面收到了电磁信号
All of a sudden, I'm getting electromagnetic readings up the wazoo.
- 现在应该是鬼片中的闹鬼了 - 谁是鬼魂 迪恩？它想要什么呢？
- It's a legit haunting now. - Who's the ghost, Dean? What's it want?
我想我们应该看一看 布拉德死时候的影片录像
I don't know. I think we should take a look at Brad's death scene.
- 你在哪里拿到的这盘DVD？- 这叫做毛片
Hey, where'd you get this DVD? - They're called dailies.
我从辛迪那里拿的 她和德鲁一起负责这些
I got it from Cindy. She's got this on-and-off thing with Drew.
他帮我复制了一盘
He dubbed me an extra copy.
好了 这里就是那家伙从棚顶掉下来那段
Here's where the guy fell through the roof.
好了
Right.
好吧 现在开始
All right, here we go.
他们一定是有顺风耳
They must have super hearing.
等等 退后 退后
Hey, wait. Go back. Go back.
再后点 再后点 好 对了
Right after Right after Yeah, right.
等等
Wait.
那里
There.
这就像的重复
It's like Three Men and a Baby all over again.
塞莱克 旦森和嘉顿伯格 还有… 我不知道谁饰演的孩子
Selleck, Danson and Guttenberg. And I don't know who played the baby.
你的重点是什么？
What's your point?
人们说电影里有一个场景… 摄像机拍下了一只鬼
There's a scene where people say that the camera caught a ghost on film.
很显然是在场景中的背景那里…
In the background of one scene...
有一个没有人认识的男孩 鬼魂摄像机
there was this boy that nobody remembers from set. Spirit photography.
我从前见过她
I've seen her before.
这个 看看这个
Here, check this out.
是的 去找奥奇
Yeah, go for Ozzy.
不 我不知道达拉在哪 我想她去洗手间了
No, I don't have a 20 on Tara. I think she's 10-100.
好的 收到
Okay, copy that.
对不起 你刚刚说什么？
I'm sorry, what were you saying?
伊莉斯·迦蒙德 三十年代的小影星
Elise Drummond. Starlet back in the '30s.
和电影工作室的执行总裁有段恋情
Had an affair with a studio exec.
他对她腻烦之后 开除了她 令她贫困潦倒
He uses her up, fires her, leaves her destitute.
伊莉斯在9号摄影棚的木椽上 上吊自杀了 就死在他们拍摄的时候
So Elise hangs herself from Stage 9's rafters right into a scene they're shooting.
就像我们的布拉德一样
Like our man Brad.
- 所以 她出现是想让工作室的电影拍不成吗？- 可能吧
- What, she's got it in for the studio brass? - Possibly.
我是说 这是一种动机 而且布拉德死的方式 和她的完全一样
I mean, it's a motive, and Brad's death matches hers exactly.
我们今晚开挖 好吗？
We're digging tonight, aren't we?
大家听着 结束了 明天早上6点全体人员继续
That's a wrap, people. Six a.m. call for crew tomorrow.
大家干的漂亮
Great work, everybody.
麦克基 你是个天才
McG, you're a genius.
- 你真的是泰然自若 手到擒来 - 晚安 杰伊
- You're kicking ass and taking names. - Night, Jay.
好的
Yeah.
哪条路？
Which way?
呃… 那边
Uh, over here.
- 嘿 - 什么？
- Hey. - Yeah.
这张地图真的值5块钱
Ha. This map is totally worth the 5 bucks.
当我们这里结束以后… 我们得去看看乔尼·雷蒙的墓地
We gotta go check out Johnny Ramone's grave when we're done here.
你想把他也挖出来？
You wanna dig him up too?
闭上你的臭嘴 野蛮人
Bite your tongue, heathen.
那个很酷
That's cool.
迪恩 我明白为什么是现在？
Dean, what I don't get is why now?
在75年之后 伊莉斯·迦蒙德就突然变得嗜杀如命了
After 75 years, Elise Drummond suddenly goes homicidal,
你知道 为什么是这部电影？
you know. Why this movie?
也许她因为他们拍摄的是 恐怖影片而发疯吧
Maybe she's mad they're making a scary ghost flick.
- 真的有那么恐怖吗？- 我们到了
- Come on, is it really that scary? - Here we go.
是的
Yeah.
- 好了 - 开动吧
- All right. - Yahtzee.
我知道 不 我讨厌麦克基的日程安排
I know. No, I frigging hate McG's dailies.
我不能控制那个家伙 我告诉你 下一个我会自己导演的
I can't control the guy. I'm telling you, next one, I'm directing myself.
什么 你？
What, you?
不 鲍勃 我喜欢你
No, Bob. You, I love.
你是个天才 你拍电影是泰然自若 手到擒来
You're a genius, you're kicking ass and taking names.
是的 好 是 晚点再给你电话 宝贝
Yeah, okay. Yeah, talk to you later, babe. Uh-huh.
什么家伙
What a dick.
哦 太棒了
Oh, great.
嗨 伙计们
Hey, guys.
制片人还在这儿 有人吗
Producer walking here. Hello?
嘿
Hey.
嘿 伙计
Hey, pal.
你能… 告诉我出口在哪里吗？我这儿什么都看不到
Can you, uh, show me to the exit? I can't see a damn thing here.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 你这家伙 我在和你说话 这里可能会有人受伤的
Hey, putz, I'm talking to you. Somebody could get hurt here.
见鬼
What the hell?
不
No!
他们永远不会原谅
They never forgive.
他们永远不会忘记
They never forget
米奇？艾希莉？
Mitch? Ashley?
今年夏天 他们再一次回来了…
And this summer, they're coming back again to settle the score, again.
你在这吗？
You out here?
艾希莉和托德 他们已经死了 温迪 他们已经死了
Ashley and Todd, they're dead. Wendy, they're dead.
这些混蛋不带我们 就这么走了
These bastards aren't taking us. Not without a fight.
我现在就要离开这里了 布罗迪
I'm getting out of here now! Brodie!
从麦田屠杀者 怪物卡车
From the producers Of Cornfield Massacre, Monster Truck.
还有查利的天使 查利的天使 全力以赴…
And the director of Charlie's Angels, Charlie's Angels:Full Throttle...
和来自地狱的阴霾 恐怖新体验
and Hell Hazers, comes a new experience in terror.
我们一定把他们从地狱回来带回来
We must've brought them back. Back from hell. Again.
地狱阴霾II 清算
Hell Hazers II: The Reckoning.
这本片子还没有被打分
This film is not yet rated.
根据一个粉丝的说法
Run-in with a giant fan.
同样的事情在66年时 也发生在一个电工身上
Same thing happened to an electrician back in '66.
- 一个叫比利·比尔德的家伙 - 到底怎么回事呢 伙计
- Guy named Billy Beard. - What the hell, dude?
我不知道 这一次看上去 不像是伊莉斯干的
I don't know. Doesn't seem like Elise this time. It's not her m.o.
我们已经烧了她了 我们是在对付另外一个鬼？
We torched her. Are we dealing with another ghost?
- 可能是 - 但是这些东西 通常不会小组行动的
- Maybe. - Yeah, these things don't usually tag team.
所有人 都过来一下 好吗？
Everybody, gather around, okay?
我有件事要宣布一下 帮我拿着
Got an announcement to make. Hold that for me.
所有人
Everyone...
靠近一点
huddle in.
因为昨晚杰伊的意外
In light of Jay's accident last night...
以及要同当局进行协调合作
and in cooperation with the authorities...
我们要停工几天
we're shutting down production for a few days.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
听着 我不会对你们说谎 这个礼拜我们是遇到了一些挫折
Look, I'm not gonna lie to you, we've had a few setbacks this week.
但是我们都知道杰伊和布拉德 最想要什么
But we all know what Jay and Brad wanted more than anything...
那就是让地狱阴霾II 清算
and that was to see Hell Hazers II: The Reckoning...
在全美的大银幕上公映
on screens all across America.
现在 是我们欠他们 所以要继续努力
Now, we owe it to them to go on and to pull together...
团结一心 拍摄好这部该死的电影 恩？
and make this damn movie, huh?
但是… 但是… 不是今天
But not-Not today.
回家去 有人会给你们打电话的
Go home. Someone will call you.
我会带着那个的
Okay, I'll take that.
温蒂 不要
Wendy, don't.
怎么了？你在害怕吗？怕鬼？
What, are you afraid of ghosts?
好了啦 这会很好玩的
Come on, it'll be fun.
对不起 我还能再去吗
Sorry, can I go again?
- 嘿 - 好的
- Hey. - Okay.
嘿
Hey.
那么 你找到那个电工埋哪儿了吗？
So you find out where the electrician's buried?
他没埋在哪儿 比利·伯德是被火化的
He wasn't. Billy Beard was cremated.
太好了 现在怎么办？
Great. Now what?
不知道
No idea.
有任何鬼影在母带里吗？
Any more ghost cameos in the dailies?
前六个小时没有
Not in the first six hours.
你知道吗 也许那些鬼魂
You know, maybe the spirits are...
想让这部电影叫停 因为他们认为电影很讨厌
trying to shut down the movie because they think it sucks.
因为 我的意思是 确实挺讨厌的
Because, I mean, it kind of does.
"来吧" "会很有趣的"那句开始
McG "Come on, it'll be fun."
来吧 这会很有趣的
Come on, it'll be fun.
注意听咒语
Listen to the invocation.
迪恩 那是真的咒语
Dean, that's the real deal.
一个召唤式的巫术咒语
A necromantic summoning ritual.
这种东西出现在一部 好莱坞电影里是要干嘛？
What the hell is that doing in a Hollywood movie?
不 亲爱的 我们要停工几天 再开工的时间不定
No, dude, we're down for a few days. Force majeure. Yeah.
很好 这会给我时间去 弄一下那个时间旅行的东西
It's cool, it gives me time to pitch that time-travel thing.
是的 好吧 听着 你再打给我谈这件事情 好吗？我是说真的
Yeah. All right, well, look, get back to me on this, seriously.
不 我是认真的
No, I'm serious.
老兄 你是认真的吗？因为我是讲真的
Dude, are you serious? Because I'm serious.
好吧 很好
All right, cool.
伙计们 我们已经停工了 你们还在这干嘛？
Guys, we're all shut down. What are you still doing here?
是的 呃…
Yeah, um, just...
真的很抱歉 老兄 我… 我们就是控制不了自己
Sorry, man. We-We-We couldn't help ourselves.
我们得告诉你我们看了剧本
We just had to tell you that we read the script.
然后？
And?
是的
Yeah.
- 精彩绝伦 - 精彩绝伦
- It's, uh-It's awesome. - Awesome.
- 真的精彩绝伦 - 我知道 真的是无以伦比的 对吧？
Really awesome. - I know, it's pretty rocking, right?
- 我很高兴你们喜欢它 - 是的 我真的很喜欢所有
- I'm glad you guys liked it. - Yeah, I really liked, uh...
在细节方面的注重
all the attention to detail.
伙计 没错 那就是我的特点
Dude, right on, that's my thing.
我的意思是 你知道的 算是我的罪恶好了 但那就是我
I mean, color me guilty, but that is me.
我是个绝对的细节专家
I mean, I'm a total detail buff.
是的 我看的出来 从你导演的方式 所有那些召唤仪式
No, I can tell. The way you worked in all those Enochian summoning rituals...
还有那些正统语言还有…
in all the authentic language, and...
什么 你是说那些拉丁语的废话？
What, you mean that Latin crap?
不 兄弟 那是沃尔特做的
No, man. That's Walter.
沃尔特·狄克逊 原作者
Walter Dixon, the original writer.
你喜欢那些垃圾？
You like that garbage?
等一下 沃尔特？那个私人助理沃尔特？
Wait, Walter the PA, Walter?
不 他不是私人助理 他的合约有一条条款 让他能来拍摄现场
He's not a PA. He's got a clause in his contract that allows him to come on set.
但是是他写的那些咒语？
But he wrote the invocations?
他写了一本很呆的剧本 没剧情的铺垫
He wrote a whack-job screenplay. There's no pace...
没有爱情看点 都是些疯子一样的说明
no love interest, it's all wackadoo exposition.
我要剪切掉 大概90%的东西去让它能被读懂
I cut like 90 percent of it to make it readable.
然后另外10%去让它变得好看
Another 10 percent to make it good.
应该保存沃尔特的原始剧本的 事实上还挺不错的
Should've kept Walter's original script. It's actually pretty good.
是啊
Yeah.
读上去像是召唤术的学习手册一样
And it reads like a how-to manual of conjuration.
就像是一本教你 如何召唤鬼魂的教科书
Like a textbook on how to summon ghosts
然后让它们为你去做任何事
and get them to do whatever you want.
- 是啊 就像去杀人 - 是的
- Yeah, like kill people. - Yep.
所以假设在某段时期 沃尔特学了一些非常黑暗的巫术
Let's say somewhere down the line Walter learned some Black Magic.
是的 然后我们假设 他被那些人给惹火了 因为他们搞砸了他的电影
Yeah, and let's say he's pissed at these people for wrecking his movie.
动机和手段都有了
Motive and means.
值得去查清楚
It's worth checking out.
那么
So...
你想要会面？
you wanted to meet?
嘿 我有点忙呢 兄弟 我在改剧本
Hey, I'm a little busy here, buddy. I'm working on a script.
哦 是啊 你们经常改动剧本
Oh, yeah, you guys worked on it a lot.
需要改动 那么为什么我们不能 在我的办公室里谈这些呢？
It needed work. Why couldn't we have done this in my office?
你知道 历史 那些在我的草稿里的知识 都是完全准确的
You know the history, the lore in my draft was completely accurate.
我们可以在刚开始的时候 就把一切都做对的
We could've gotten it right for the first time ever...
在这里 这个镇的堕落之地
in this whorehouse of a town.
但是把它当垃圾一样粉碎了
But you tore it to shreds.
你用艳俗和狗屁一样的玩笑来代替它
You replaced it with cleavage and fart jokes.
那些都是真实
It was real.
谁在乎真实不真实？
Who gives a rat's ass about real?
我们在谈论鬼 沃尔特 根本就没有那种东西
We're talking about ghosts here, there's no such thing.
那就是你搞错的地方 马丁
That's where you're wrong, Martin.
好了 白痴 会面结束
Okay, nut job. End of meeting.
噢 天啊 不 求你 不要
Oh, God, no. Please, no.
你毁了它 马丁 我致力于的所有的东西
You ruined it, Martin. Everything I worked for.
哦 上帝 沃尔特
Oh, God! Walter!
现在你就要知道做鬼的滋味了
You're gonna find out what being a ghost is like.
沃尔特 求你
Walter, please!
沃尔特 救我 救命
Walter, help me!
你真是个非同一般的私人助理
You are one hell of a PA.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I know.
你们要干什么？
What are you doing?
这句话该我来问你 沃尔特
I could ask you the same thing.Walter.
把那些鬼魂召唤回来
Raising these spirits from the dead...
让他们为你杀人 那是在玩火 沃尔特
making them murder for you, that's playing with fire, Walter.
你不明白
You don't understand.
你知道吗？你是对的 我不明白
You know what, you're right, I don't understand.
等等 听着 你倾注你的一切在某件事上
Wait, look, you put your heart and soul into something.
多少年的努力 多少年 然后他们拿走了它
Years of hard work. Years. And then they take it...
并且完全的毁它
and they crap all over it!
然后 然后他们还希望你笑着跟他们说谢谢
And then-And then they want you to smile and say thank you.
沃尔特 听着 那只是部电影 仅仅如此
Walter, listen, it's just a movie. That's it.
你瞧
Look...
我对你们没有敌意 你们与此无关
I got nothing against you, man. You're not part of this.
求你们了 求求你们了 离开吧
Just please, please, just leave.
但是马丁要留下
But Martings gotta stay.
对不起 不能这么做
Sorry, can't do that.
不是说我们喜欢他或者怎么样 这是原则问题
It's not that we like him or anything, it's just a matter of principle.
那么我也对不起了
Then I'm sorry too.
沃尔特 沃尔特 求你… 不要
Walter. Walter, pl-Don't.
萨姆
Sam!
狗娘…
Son of a..
来吧 来吧
Come on, come on.
快 快 快走
Come on, come on, move.
"来海边吧" "我们聚一起 乐一乐"
"Come to the coast, we'll get together, have a few laughs."
哦 可恶
Oh, man.
- 我简直不能相信 居然真的有鬼 - 什么让你认为这世界上没鬼的？
- I can't believe these ghosts are real. What makes you say that?
但是我不明白
I don't understand.
沃尔特是怎么控制它们的？
How is Walter controlling them?
可能是那个护身符
Probably with that talisman.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
如果摄像机能捕捉到 这些东西的影像…
I mean, if film cameras pick these suckers up, then...
可能… 呃…
maybe, uh...
迪恩 那边
Dean, right there!
打中了
Got him.
嘿 在那边
Hey, right there!
- 拿着 知道怎么用了吗？- 是的
- Here, you get the idea? - Yeah.
好了 你们拖着它们 我去追沃尔特
All right, you hold them off, I'm going after Walter.
- 我没法相信还有灵魂存在 - 是有灵魂的 好吗
- I cannot believe there's an afterlife. - There's an afterlife, all right.
但是通常都是让人如坐针毡
But mostly it's a pain in the ass.
那里
There!
结束了 沃尔特
It's over, Walter.
现在 把那东西给我
Now, give it to me.
那里 好了 现在没人可以得到它了
There, okay, now no one can have it.
- 如果我是你的话我绝不会这么做 - 是吗？
- I wouldn't have done that if I were you. - Oh, yeah?
- 是的 - 为什么不？
- Yeah. - And why not?
因为你刚刚释放了它们
Because you just freed them.
我们现在无法阻止它们了
We can't stop them now.
沃尔特 你把它们带了回来…
Walter, you brought them back...
强迫它们杀人
forced them to murder.
它们不会对你有好感的
They're not gonna be very happy with you.
是吗？所以呢 为什么没有？
Yeah, so why not?
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
那里
There!
但是我不明白 为什么灵魂能显现在手机相机上
I don't understand, how can the spirits appear in the camera phone?
一定是摄相机能捕捉到… 我们的眼睛捕捉不到的频率
The video must pick up their frequencies in a way that our eyes can't.
在那里
Right there.
停机 哦 收录好那段 那会放到电影里去
Cut! Oh, print that one. That's in the movie.
哦 我爱它 孩子们 我爱它
Oh, loved it, kids. Loved it.
你发现了鬼魂的存在 然后这就是你用它所做的？
You find out there's an afterlife, and this is what you do with it?
我需要在剧本上加点亮点嘛
I needed a little jazz on the page.
你真是个非同一般的私人助理
You're one hell of a PA.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿
Hi.
上帝啊 我爱这个小镇
God, I love this town.